#### CONTACT



07975 697134



jackdomleo7@hotmail.com



https://jackdomleo.dev



28 Melksham Road, Nottingham, UK NG5 5RX

## SOCIAL

in

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jack-domleo

#### SKILLS

- → Basic use of Adobe Creative Cloud software including Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat and more.
- → Confident in developing and researching JavaScript, React JS and jQuery.
- → Confident in identifying SEO issues and acting to improve them.
- → Competent in working in a team to collaborate ideas towards the end product.
- → Confident in using and developing web applications using different programming languages and frameworks. I have experience with:
  - HTML 5, CSS 3, Bootstrap 4, Grav CMS
  - JavaScript, jQuery, React JS, Electron JS
  - o Python
  - o Git (GitHub, BitBucket)
  - Command Line
  - Flow (Project/Task Management System)
  - o Mailchimp

# Jack Domleo

Junior Web Developer

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am an energetic and enthusiastic person with six months experience working in IT and development in the airline industry. My present career aim is to progress in IT development and complete an apprenticeship course to achieve a development related qualification. I enjoy a challenge and will tackle anything thrown at me. I enjoy the environment of working in IT and I find the development work interesting and satisfying. The opportunity to learn new skills and work with new technologies is particularly attractive to me.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# IT Developer Apprentice

Sept 2018 - Feb 2019

flybmi, East Midlands Airport

As an IT Developer Apprentice for this airline, my responsibilities included:

- Worked towards BCS Level 3 in Software Development
- Developed new programs from a design specification using frameworks such as Bootstrap 4, Grav CMS, Core UI and Electron JS
- Created new templates for the CMS and maintaining the flybmi.com website

During my time at flybmi, I gained 6 months' worth of knowledge and experience working in the airline industry and working together with other employees to develop an end product.

Reason for leaving: Company filed for administration.

#### Retail Assistant

June 2017 - Aug 2018

Primark, Nottingham

As a Retail Assistant for this high street clothing company, my responsibilities included:

- Answering customer queries and maintaining quality customer service
- Ensuring items are restocked and displayed effectively
- Training new starters with their duties (till training, department training)

During my time at Primark, I gained skills and experience in teamwork, customer service/engagement and merchandising.

Reason for leaving: Found an apprenticeship at flybmi to begin my career

#### REFERENCES



Tim Moore Head of IT flybmi 07503 914916 timjimmoore@gmail.com



George Smith Digital Systems Manager flybmi 07415 371200



Lee Robinson Manager Primark 0115 958 0817

#### HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- → Walking
- → Travelling & Days Out
- → Nottingham Panthers Ice Hockey games

## ACHIEVEMENTS

- → Young Enterprise
  - Elected managing director and finance director
  - Learned leadership, organisational and budgeting skills
- → Air Cadet Organisation
  - Completed NNAS, basic first aid and radio communication courses
- → Bronze & Silver DofE
  - Required teamwork, communication and survival skills
- → Black Belt
  - Achieved Black Belt in Karate, which took dedication
- $\rightarrow$  Ice Hockey & Ice Skating
  - Completed up to UK Skate level 5 in ice skating and level 6 in ice hockey

## Office Assistant

JND Accounting, Nottingham

As an Office Assistant for this small firm, my responsibilities included:

- Accurately inputting and transferring client data into new database system
- Pro-actively ensuring organisation of the office
- Reliably filing important client documents into relevant folders

Key achievements included learning basic accountancy skills and office organisation.

**Reason for leaving:** This was a temporary position until they could hire an apprentice.

### EDUCATION

The Redhill Academy Sixth Form, Nottingham	2016-2018
A-level Computer Science	В
A-level Mathematics	В
A-level Physics	D
AS Chemistry	В

#### The Redhill Academy, Nottingham

2013-2016

GCSE Mathematics	A*
GCSE Physics	A*
GCSE German	A
GCSE Biology	A
GCSE Computer Science	В
GCSE Chemistry	В
GCSE Business Studies	В
GCSE English Language	В
GCSE English Literature	С
GCSE Further Mathematics	С

## QUALIFICATIONS

BCS Level 2 ECDL in IT Application (The Redhill Academy)	Distinction*
BCS Level 3 Software Development Technician (Geason Training)	Paused due to flybmi filing for administration
Google Digital Garage	In progress

# DRIVING LICENSE

Holder of a clean UK manual & automatic driving license since 22<sup>nd</sup> Nov 2017.